(Howard:)...are two not unattractive
middle-school teachers...
(Howard:)...who reek of desperation.
(Raj:)-Wonderful. How old are they?
-I don't know, 50, 55?
Oh, menopause. Heh.
(Raj:)Nature's birth control.
(Leonard:)Come on. You guys can't be that hard up.
(Howard:)-I am.
-Yeah, me too.
(Howard:)Look, they gave me homemade cookies.
(Leonard:)Of course they did.
That's what grandmothers do.
(Raj:)-So, what are we waiting for?
-Relax.
(Howard:)I said we'd stop by a little later,
after they have their nap.
(Raj:)-Good idea. They'll be refreshed.
HOWARD: Yeah.
(Howard:)-Cookie?
-Thank you.
RAJESH:
Mmm.
(Leonard:)-Mm. Not bad.
-Yeah, very tasty.
(Raj:)Tell me more about these teachers.
(Howard:)Not much to tell.
They had a VW Microbus...
(Howard:)...and were wearing
tie-dyed Grateful Dead T-shirts.
Huh. Hm.
(Raj:)Good cookies.